( rooster crows )
( crowing )
WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT?
( crowing )
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
IS THAT YOU?
( crowing )
OH!
BOY, YOU ARE REALLY
NOT A MORNING PERSON.
BACK OFF!
GET UP! GET UP! GET UP!
GET UP! GET UP!
WHAT IS THAT NOISE?
YOU.
IT'S THE CHICK.
SHE'S GOING
THROUGH SOME CHANGES.
WHAT KIND
OF CHANGES?
THE VET SEEMS TO THINK
THAT SHE'S BECOMING
A ROOSTER.
( crowing )
WE'RE GETTING
A SECOND OPINION.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING SHOPPING
AT 8:00 IN
THE MORNING?
WELL, I'VE BEEN UP
SINCE 6:00
THANKS TO SOMEBODY'S
DUMB-ASS ROOSTER.
GUYS, YOU REALLY
SHOULD GET RID
OF THOSE ANIMALS.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE LIVING
IN AN APARTMENT.
ESPECIALLY NOT WITH ALL THESE
KNIVES AND COOKBOOKS AROUND.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO
TO THE FERTILITY DOCTOR
AND SEE IF I'M READY TO HAVE
FRANK AND ALICE'S EMBRYO
TRANSFERRED INTO MY UTERUS.
NOW, HOW WILL THEY KNOW
IF YOU'RE READY?
THEY'RE GOING TO SEE
IF MY ENDOMETRIAL LAYER
IS THICK.
WELL, I CAN, UH, CHECK THAT
FOR YOU.
OKAY, EVERYONE, THINK THICK.
GOOD LUCK.
HEY!
WISH ME LUCK.
OH... GOOD LUCK.
AND I'M STILL RIGHT.
THAT IS SO NOT TRUE.
WHAT?
SHE'S MAD BECAUSE I KNOW
TODAY'S HER LAUNDRY DAY
AND THAT MEANS SHE'S WEARING
HER OLD LADY UNDERPANTS.
WELL, I CAN
CHECK THAT FOR YOU.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT YOU THINK
THAT YOU AND CHANDLER
KNOW ME AND RACHEL BETTER
THAN WE KNOW YOU.
WELL, WE DO.
YOU CAN ONLY EAT TIC TACS
IN EVEN NUMBERS.
YEAH, WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
AND YOU...
ROSS, I BELIEVE IF
YOU CHECK RACHEL'S BAG
YOU WILL FIND A HALF-EATEN BOX
OF COOKIES IN THERE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
THESE ARE NOT.
SO NOT IMPRESSED.
EVERYBODY SNACKS
WHEN THEY SHOP.
OH, YEAH?
ROSS, HOW MANY ITEMS
LEFT IN THAT BAG?
FIVE.
OKAY, TEN BUCKS SAYS
THAT WE CAN NAME
EVERY ITEM IN THAT BAG.
HOW MANY GUESSES DO YOU GET?
SIX.
CHALLENGE EXTENDED.
DEAL.
CHALLENGE ACCEPTED.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL START WITH...
APPLES.
WE'LL BE STARTING WITH APPLES.
STOP THAT NOW.
YES.
OKAY, UH, TORTILLA
CHIPS, YOGURT...
DIET SODA...
YES, YES...
YES.
ORANGE JUICE.
THERE'S NO ORANGE JUICE
IN THERE.
WE WIN!
THEY HAVE ANOTHER GUESS.
OKAY, WELL, WE WON THAT ONE.
OKAY, THE LAST THING IS...
OOH, OOH! OOH! OOH, OOH!
NO. NO. NOT FOR LIKE
ANOTHER TWO WEEKS.
I GOT IT.
SCOTCH...
TAPE.
HA!
HOW DID YOU KNOW
SHE WOULD BUY SCOTCH TAPE?
WELL, WE USED UP THEIRS
LAST NIGHT MAKING SCARY FACES.
OH, MAN.
ALL RIGHT, TEN BUCKS.
FORK IT OVER.
COUGH IT UP.
PAY THE PIPER.
GIVE ME IT.
THAT DOES NOT MEAN
YOU KNOW US BETTER.
I WANT A REMATCH.
AND NONE OF THESE
STUPID GROCERY QUESTIONS.
REAL PERSONAL QUESTIONS.
YEAH, AND THE WINNER
GETS A HUNDRED BUCKS.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
ARE YOU SCARED?
( fearfully ):
NO.
OKAY, WHO MAKES UP
THE QUESTIONS?
ROSS'LL DO IT.
OH, SURE,
IT'S NOT LIKE HE HAS
A JOB OR A CHILD
OR A LIFE OF HIS OWN.
WELL, FINE.
WE'LL ASK PHOEBE.
NO. I WANT TO PLAY.
LOOKS LIKE
YOUR UTERUS
IS READY FOR
IMPLANTATION.
OH, I KNEW IT.
I FELT REALLY THICK
THIS MORNING.
WELL, OKAY,
SO, WHAT'S NOW?
GO-GO GET THE EGGS.
PUT THEM IN THERE.
OKAY. IT'LL TAKE
JUST A LITTLE WHILE
TO PREPARE THE EMBRYOS.
EMBRYOS?
AS IN MORE THAN ONE.
FIVE, ACTUALLY.
FIVE? OKAY,
WHERE AM I GIVING BIRTH?
IN A HOSPITAL
OR A BIG BOX UNDER THE STAIRS?
WE DO FIVE
BECAUSE THAT GIVES YOU
A 25% CHANCE
THAT AT LEAST
ONE WILL ATTACH.
THAT'S IT? 25 PERCENT?
THAT MEANS THAT IT'S
LIKE 75 PERCENT CHANCE
OF NO BABY AT ALL?
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
I WAS THINKING.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS
IF YOU STUFF 200
OF THEM IN THERE?
SWEETIE,
NOW, SHE'S A WOMAN
NOT A GUM BALL MACHINE.
OKAY, WELL, DON'T
WORRY, YOU GUYS
'CAUSE I'M GOING TO DO THIS
AS MANY TIMES AS IT TAKES
TO GET IT RIGHT.
WELL, SEE, THE THING IS
WE KIND OF ONLY HAVE
ONE SHOT.
IT COSTS $16,000
EACH TIME YOU DO THIS.
SO, UM...
WE'RE KIND OF USING
ALL THE MONEY WE HAVE
TO DO IT
JUST THIS ONE TIME.
WHOA!
THAT'S... OKAY, THAT'S
A LOT OF PRESSURE
ON ME AND MY UTERUS.
SO, WELL, OKAY...
SO, MAYBE THERE'S
SOMETHING I CAN DO
YOU KNOW
JUST TO, LIKE, HELP
MAKE SURE I GET PREGNANT.
NO. I'M SORRY.
WOW. YOU GUYS
REALLY DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
WHY DON'T YOU GET DRUNK?
THAT WORKED
FOR A BUNCH OF GIRLS
IN MY HIGH SCHOOL.
HEY, GUYS,
DO YOU REALIZE
THAT ANY MINUTE NOW,
PHOEBE COULD BE PREGNANT.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
IT'S SUCH A HUGE,
LIFE-ALTERING THING.
I KNOW.
IT IS.
THE TEST IS READY.
( cheering )
OKAY, EACH TEAM WILL
ANSWER TEN QUESTIONS.
THE FIRST TEAM TO ANSWER
THE MOST QUESTIONS WINS.
THE CATEGORIES ARE
"FEARS AND PET PEEVES"
"ANCIENT HISTORY"
"LITERATURE"
AND "IT'S ALL RELATIVE."
NOW...
THE COIN TOSS,
TO SEE WHO GOES FIRST.
OKAY...
SOMEBODY CALL IT THIS TIME.
YEAH. OKAY.
TAILS!
IT'S HEADS.
YES, IT IS!
GENTLEMEN, PICK YOUR CATEGORY.
"FEARS AND PET PEEVES."
"WHAT IS MONICA'S
BIGGEST PET PEEVE?"
ANIMALS DRESSED AS HUMANS.
Ross:
THAT'S CORRECT.
LADIES?
SAME CATEGORY.
"ACCORDING TO CHANDLER
WHAT PHENOMENON SCARES
THE BEJEEZUS OUT OF HIM?"
MICHAEL FLATLEY,
LORD OF THE DANCE.
THAT IS CORRECT.
AH!
WHOO!
THE IRISH JIG GUY?
HIS LEGS FLAIL ABOUT
AS IF INDEPENDENT
FROM HIS BODY.
AW!
GENTLEMEN, YOUR PICK.
"IT'S ALL RELATIVE."
"MONICA AND I HAD
A GRANDMOTHER WHO DIED.
"YOU BOTH WENT
TO HER FUNERAL.
NAME THAT GRANDMOTHER."
NANA?
SHE HAS A REAL NAME.
-ALTHEA!
-ALTHEA? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I TOOK A SHOT.
WITH ALTHEA?
ALTHEA IS CORRECT.
NICE SHOOTING!
WE'LL TAKE
"LITERATURE!"
"EVERY WEEK THE TV GUIDE
"COMES TO CHANDLER
AND JOEY'S APARTMENT.
WHAT NAME APPEARS
ON THE ADDRESS LABEL?"
CHANDLER GETS IT!
IT'S CHANDLER BING!
NO!
I'M AFRAID THE TV GUIDE
COMES TO "CHANANDLER BONG."
I KNEW THAT.
RACHEL, USE YOUR HEAD.
ACTUALLY, IT'S
"MISS CHANANDLER BONG."
HELLO, TEENY EMBRYOS.
WELL, I'M PHOEBE BUFFAY. HI.
I'M-I'M HOPING TO BE YOUR UTERUS
FOR THE NEXT NINE MONTHS, SO...
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT WE'RE
DOING THIS FOR FRANK AND ALICE
WHO YOU KNOW--
YOU'VE BEEN THERE.
UM...
YOU KNOW, THEY WANT YOU SO MUCH.
SO WHEN YOU GUYS GET IN THERE,
REALLY GRAB ON.
OKAY, AND... AND I PROMISE
THAT I'LL KEEP YOU
SAFE AND WARM
UNTIL, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE READY
TO HAVE THEM TAKE YOU HOME.
SO...
OKAY.
OH, AND ALSO,
NEXT TIME YOU SEE ME
IF I'M SCREAMING, DON'T WORRY.
THAT'S WHAT'S SUPPOSED
TO HAPPEN.
( knocking )
READY?
UH-HUH.
GOOD LUCK.
ALL RIGHT.
THE SCORE IS NINE TO EIGHT
IN FAVOR OF THE GUYS.
LADIES, IF YOU MISS THIS,
THE GAME IS THEIRS.
PICK YOUR CATEGORY.
"IT'S ALL RELATIVE!"
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SHOUT EVERYTHING.
I'M SORRY!
OOH.
"WHAT IS THE NAME
OF CHANDLER'S FATHER'S
LAS VEGAS ALL-MALE BURLESQUE?"
VIVA LAS GAYGAS!
UNFORTUNATELY,
THAT IS CORRECT.
YES!
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE A TIE.
LUCKILY, I'VE PREPARED
FOR SUCH AN EVENT.
THE LIGHTNING ROUND!
OH!
3O SECONDS.
ALL THE QUESTIONS
YOU CAN ANSWER.
YOU GUYS ARE DEAD.
I AM SO GOOD
AT LIGHTNING ROUNDS.
I MAJORED
IN LIGHTNING ROUNDS, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE GOING TO DESTROY YOU.
WANT TO BET?
I'M SO CONFUSED
AS TO WHAT
WE'VE BEEN DOING SO FAR.
HOW ABOUT WE PLAY
FOR MORE MONEY?
SAY, 150?
ONE HUNDRED AND
FIFTY DOLLARS.
SAY, 200?
TWO HUNDRED DOLLARS.
YOU'RE DOING IT AGAIN.
EXCUSE ME.
MONICA, I DON'T WANT
TO LOSE $200.
WE WON'T.
300?
MONICA!
I'M JUST TRYING
TO SPICE IT UP.
OKAY, SO THEN PLAY
FOR SOME PEPPER.
STOP SPENDING MY MONEY.
I GOT IT.
HOW ABOUT IF WE WIN
THEY HAVE TO GET RID
OF THE ROOSTER?
OOH, THAT'S INTERESTING.
HEY, NO WAY.
THAT ROOSTER'S FAMILY.
THROW IN THE DUCK.
THE DUCK DOESN'T
MAKE ANY NOISE.
WELL, HE GETS
THE OTHER ONE ALL RILED UP.
LOOK, WE ARE NOT...
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON.
IF YOU WIN, WE'LL
GIVE UP THE BIRDS.
GAH!
BUT IF WE WIN...
WE GET YOUR APARTMENT.
OOH.
DEAL!
MONICA, BETTING
THE APARTMENT?
I HAVE NOT MISSED ONE QUESTION
THE WHOLE GAME.
I OWN THIS GAME!
LOOK AT MY HAND.
ARE THE ANSWERS
WRITTEN ON THERE?
NO! STEADY AS A ROCK.
NOW, ARE YOU WITH ME?
HUH! LET'S DO IT!
COME ON!
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, GENTLEMEN,
YOU'RE UP FIRST.
OKAY.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS.
THE LIGHTNING ROUND
BEGINS... STOP IT.
NOW. WHAT
WAS MONICA'S NICKNAME
WHEN SHE WAS
A FIELD HOCKEY GOALIE?
"BIG FAT GOALIE."
CORRECT.
RACHEL CLAIMS
THIS IS HER FAVORITE MOVIE.
DANGEROUS LIAISONS.
HER ACTUAL FAVORITE MOVIE IS?
WEEKEND AT BERNIE'S.
CORRECT.
IN WHAT PART OF HER BODY
DID MONICA GET A PENCIL STUCK
AT AGE 14?
OH!
EW! NO!
HER EAR!
ALL RIGHT.
MONICA CATEGORIZES HER TOWELS.
HOW MANY CATEGORIES ARE THERE?
"EVERYDAY USE."
"GUEST."
"FANCY."
"FANCY GUEST."
TWO SECONDS.
D'UH, 11?!
( beeping )
11. UNBELIEVABLE.
11 IS CORRECT.
YES!
( laughing )
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S FOUR
FOR THE GUYS.
LADIES, YOU'RE UP.
ALL RIGHT,
COME ON!
30 SECONDS ON THE CLOCK.
FIVE CORRECT QUESTIONS
WINS THE GAME.
THE LIGHTNING ROUND
BEGINS...
NOW.
WHAT IS JOEY'S FAVORITE FOOD?
SANDWICHES.
CORRECT.
CHANDLER WAS HOW OLD
WHEN HE FIRST TOUCHED
A GIRL'S BREAST?
FOURTEEN?
NO, 19.
THANKS, MAN.
JOEY HAD
AN IMAGINARY CHILDHOOD FRIEND.
HIS NAME WAS...?
MAURICE.
HIS PROFESSION WAS...?
SPACE COWBOY!
CORRECT!
WHAT IS CHANDLER BING'S JOB?
OH...!
OH, GOSH! DOES
IT HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH NUMBERS?
AND PROCESSING.
AND HE CARRIES
A BRIEFCASE.
YOU NEED THIS,
OR YOU LOSE THE GAME.
IT HAS SOMETHING
TO DO WITH TRANSPONDING.
OH, OH, HE'S
A TRANSPONDS-
TRANSPONSTER!
THAT'S NOT EVEN A WORD!
OH!
I CAN GET THIS!
I CAN...
( beeping )
NO!!!
YES!
I CALL MONICA'S ROOM.
YOU CAN'T JUST CALL
MONICA'S ROOM.
SURE, I CAN.
STANDARD SHOTGUN RULES.
I'M IN SIGHT OF THE ROOM
AND I CALLED IT.
MAN, I FEEL LIKE I'M
COMING DOWN WITH SOMETHING.
OOH.
YEAH.
BET YOU CAN'T GUESS
WHAT COLOR MY
TONSILS ARE.
I'LL BET THE APARTMENT.
I WOULD NEVER BET
THIS APARTMENT.
IT'S TOO NICE.
HEY.
OOH, PHEEBS, ARE
THEY IN THERE?
UM, YEAH, UH-HUH, I'M IMPLANTED.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
WELL, FREAKED.
IT TURNS OUT THE ODDS
ARE, LIKE, REALLY SUCKY
AND THIS IS FRANK AND ALICE'S,
LIKE, ONLY SHOT.
THEY ARE, LIKE, LITERALLY
PUTTING ALL THEIR EGGS
IN MY BASKET.
YEAH, BUT I BET
IT WORKS.
REALLY? HOW MUCH?
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO
TAKE A PREGNANCY TEST RIGHT NOW.
OH, WOW. YOU CAN TELL THIS SOON?
WELL, THE DOCTOR SAYS
IT TAKES A COUPLE DAYS
BUT MY BODY'S
ALWAYS BEEN A LITTLE FASTER
THAN WESTERN MEDICINE, SO...
( clearing throat )
OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS
ACTUALLY THINK
YOU'RE MOVING IN HERE.
WELL, BELIEVE IT, BABY.
WELL, I-I, I'M NOT MOVING.
WHAT?!
NO. IT WAS A STUPID BET.
WE WERE JUST PLAYING A GAME.
YOU CAN'T
JUST IGNORE THE BET.
IT'S A BET.
YOU BET ON A BET,
AND IF YOU LOSE
YOU LOSE THE BET.
RACH, WE HAVE TO MOVE.
IF WE HAD LOST, WE
WOULD HAVE MADE THEM
GET RID OF THE BIRDS,
RIGHT?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I HATE THIS
AS MUCH AS YOU, BUT...
IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL ANY BETTER
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
WHAT?!
"CHANANDLER BONG."
COME ON, WE STEAL
THAT TV GUIDE EVERY WEEK.
I KNEW IT!
I DON'T CARE.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
COOL. GIRL ROOMMATE.
WELL?
NOPE, NOT
KNOCKED UP YET.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
IT'S ONLY BEEN A COUPLE HOURS
SO, JUST GIVE IT SOME TIME.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
MEANWHILE
I'M GOING TO DO
WHATEVER I CAN
TO HELP THIS, SO, I'M
JUST GOING TO, YOU KNOW
LIE IN YOUR
CHAIR, OKAY?
YOU KNOW, JUST...
YEAH, GOOD.
I'M GOING TO LET GRAVITY,
YOU KNOW, DO ITS JOB.
HEY, RACH, CAN YOU GIVE
ME A HAND WITH THIS BOX?
NO! PUT THAT BOX DOWN!
WE ARE NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
THIS IS MY APARTMENT,
AND I LIKE IT!
THIS IS A "GIRLS'" APARTMENT!
THAT IS A "BOYS'" APARTMENT!
IT'S DIRTY AND IT SMELLS!
THIS IS PRETTY!
IT'S SO PRETTY!
AND LOOK,
AND IT'S PURPLE!
AND I'M TELLING YOU--
YOU WITH YOUR STEADY HAND--
I AM NOT MOVING, AND NOW
I HAVE GOT THE STEADY HAND.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU DO WHAT THE HAND SAYS!
( door shuts )
HOW'D IT GO?
I LOST OUR MATTRESSES.
( guitar strumming )
♪ ARE YOU IN THERE,
LITTLE FETUS? ♪
♪ IN NINE MONTHS,
WILL YOU COME GREET US...? ♪
♪ I WILL BUY YOU
SOME ADIDAS... ♪
( knock at door )
HI.
HEY.
OH, HI. PHOEBE, UM...
WE WERE JUST
AT THE DRUGSTORE
UM, SO WE GOT YOU
A LITTLE PRESENT.
UM, IT'S A LOLLIPOP
AND, UH, A HOME PREGNANCY TEST.
DON'T MIX THOSE UP.
YOU COULD REALLY RUIN
THAT LOLLIPOP.
SO, UM... YOU FEEL
LIKE TAKING A TEST?
THERE'S ONLY ONE QUESTION.
( goofy laughter )
A-ALL RIGHT, I WILL.
I WILL, BUT, UM,
YOU KNOW, JUST REMEMBER
THAT IT'S STILL REALLY EARLY
SO, IF IT SAYS THAT
I'M NOT PREGNANT
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I'M
NOT GOING TO GET PREGNANT
OKAY? AND, AND
JUST PLEASE
JUST SO I DON'T GO
COMPLETELY NUTS
JUST TRY NOT TO PUT
ALL YOUR HOPES ON THIS
OKAY?
OKAY.
GREAT.
( laughing )
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU ARE MEAN BOYS
WHO ARE JUST BEING MEAN.
HEY, DON'T
GET MAD AT US.
NO ONE FORCED YOU
TO RAISE THE STAKES.
THAT IS NOT TRUE!
SHE DID! SHE FORCED ME!
WE'D STILL BE HERE,
BUT YOU GOT THE QUESTION WRONG.
WELL, IT WAS
A STUPID, UNFAIR QUESTION.
DON'T BLAME
THE QUESTIONS.
WOULD YOU ALL STOP YELLING
IN OUR APARTMENT?!
YOU ARE RUINING
MOVING DAY FOR US!
STOP CALLING IT YOUR APARTMENT!
IT IS OUR APARTMENT!
( everybody yelling )
YOU GUYS, YOU GUYS,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A BABY.
THEY'RE GOING
TO HAVE A BABY!
MY SISTER'S
GOING TO HAVE MY BABY!
OKAY, BUT THIS
CAN'T BE GOOD FOR THE BABY.
( cheering )
I CAN'T FIND GARBAGE BAGS.
OH, WELL, I THINK
I SAW SOME IN HERE.
( screaming )
WHAT IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW
BUT MAYBE IF
WE KEEP THAT
DRAWER SHUT
IT'LL DIE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE LIVING HERE!
( yelling )
WHA...? WH-WHAT IS IT?!
DID YOU SEE THE SIZE
OF THE CLOSETS?!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE LIVE HERE!
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
OH...!
OH!!!